{
    "unit1": {
        "word": {
            "choice": [
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"},
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"},
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"},
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"},
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"},
                {"question": "书本的英文是？", "options": ["book", "ruler"], "answer": "book"}
            ],
            "matching": [
                { "left": "mouth", "right": "嘴巴" },
                { "left": "nose", "right": "鼻子" },
                { "left": "eye", "right": "眼睛" },
                { "left": "ear", "right": "耳朵" },
                { "left": "ruler", "right": "尺子" }
            ],
            "read_aloud": [
                {"question": "读：'I have a pencil.'", "answer": "I have a pencil."},
                {"question": "读：'I have a schoolbag.'", "answer": "I have a schoolbag."}
            ],
            "spelling": [
                {"question": "拼写: 尺子", "answer": "ruler"}
            ]
        },
        "sentence": {
            "read_aloud": [
                {"question": "Read: I have a book.", "answer": "I have a book."}
            ],
            "matching": [
                { "left": "Sit down, please.", "right": "坐下，谢谢。" },
                { "left": "Stand up, Joy.", "right": "站起来，乔伊。" },
                { "left": "eye", "right": "眼睛" },
                { "left": "ear", "right": "耳朵" },
                { "left": "ruler", "right": "尺子" }
            ],
            "choice": [
                {"question": "我有一个书包。", "options": ["I have a schoolbag.", "I have a teacher."], "answer": "I have a schoolbag."}
            ]
        }
    },
    "unit2": {
        "word": {
            "choice": [
                {"question": "耳朵的英文是？", "options": ["ear", "eye"], "answer": "ear"}
            ],
            "matching": [
                { "left": "mouth", "right": "嘴巴" },
                { "left": "nose", "right": "鼻子" },
                { "left": "eye", "right": "眼睛" },
                { "left": "ear", "right": "耳朵" },
                { "left": "ruler", "right": "尺子" },
                { "left": "face", "right": "脸" }
            ],
            "read_aloud": [
                {"question": "Read: nose", "answer": "Nose"}
            ],
            "spelling": [
                {"question": "Spell: 眼睛", "answer": "eye"}
            ]
        },
        "sentence": {
            "read_aloud": [
                {"question": "Read: Touch your ear.", "answer": "Touch your ear."}
            ],
            "matching": [
                {"left": "Open your mouth.", "right": "张开你的嘴巴。" },
                { "left": "Close your mouth.", "right": "闭上你的嘴巴。" }
            ],
            "choice": [
                {"question": "这是我的脸。", "options": ["This is my face.", "Touch your face."], "answer": "This is my face."}
            ]
        }
    }
}
